<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

<AdvancedBionicEye.label>advanced bionic eye</AdvancedBionicEye.label>
<AdvancedBionicEye.description>This advanced piece of technology allows the user to perfectly see in the dark as well as through walls. Also through clothes.</AdvancedBionicEye.description>

<AdvancedBionicArm.label>advanced bionic arm</AdvancedBionicArm.label>
<AdvancedBionicArm.description>Remember when you struggled with opening jars? Now you struggle with not breaking them instantly.</AdvancedBionicArm.description>

<AdvancedBionicLeg.label>advanced bionic leg</AdvancedBionicLeg.label>
<AdvancedBionicLeg.description>Gotta go fast!</AdvancedBionicLeg.description>

<AdvancedBionicSpine.label>advanced bionic spine</AdvancedBionicSpine.label>
<AdvancedBionicSpine.description>This durable device supports the back and makes working and walking much easier.</AdvancedBionicSpine.description>

<AdvancedBionicEar.label>advanced bionic ear</AdvancedBionicEar.label>
<AdvancedBionicEar.description>This device allows the user to hear better than bats.</AdvancedBionicEar.description>

<AdvancedBionicHand.label>advanced bionic hand</AdvancedBionicHand.label>
<AdvancedBionicHand.description>Some people would chop their own hands off just to get this gorgeous piece of tech.</AdvancedBionicHand.description>

<AdvancedBionicFoot.label>advanced bionic foot</AdvancedBionicFoot.label>
<AdvancedBionicFoot.description>Dozens of servomotors grant faster movement and ultimate comfort.</AdvancedBionicFoot.description>Foot.description>

<AdvancedBionicFinger.label>advanced bionic finger</AdvancedBionicFinger.label>
<AdvancedBionicFinger.description>Advanced bionic finger. Delicate glitterworld sensors and high-speed wireless transmitters running through the thick, yet lightweight plasteel casing ensure the best precision and grip, far surpassing that of a natural or bionic finger. Powerful enough to crush rocks like ripe tomatoes.</AdvancedBionicFinger.description>

<AdvancedBionicToe.label>advanced bionic toe</AdvancedBionicToe.label>
<AdvancedBionicToe.description>Advanced bionic toe. Delicate glitterworld sensors and high-speed wireless transmitters running through the thick, yet lightweight plasteel casing make these toes unrivalled when it comes to movement and control, far surpassing that of natural or bionic toes. Glitterworld mechanite-traction technology ensures extreme speeds even on normally unfavourable terrain, such as water.</AdvancedBionicToe.description>

<AdvancedBionicJaw.label>advanced bionic jaw</AdvancedBionicJaw.label>
<AdvancedBionicJaw.description>The voice this jaw creates is so beautiful that even mechanoids stop by to listen.</AdvancedBionicJaw.description>

<AdvancedPowerArm.label>advanced power arm</AdvancedPowerArm.label>
<AdvancedPowerArm.description>Even more unparalleled strength and dexterity, and with a sharp, retractable claws. Now it's the ultimate arm upgrade!</AdvancedPowerArm.description>

<ExoskeletonSuit.label>exoskeleton suit</ExoskeletonSuit.label>
<ExoskeletonSuit.description>A high tech device made out of two components: a light skeletal structure to relieve the back and servomotors to make the user stronger.</ExoskeletonSuit.description>

</LanguageData>