<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

<BionicEye.label>bionic eye</BionicEye.label>
<BionicEye.description>Advanced piece of technology made not only to fully replace natural eye, but also to give supernatural vision abilities.</BionicEye.description>

<BionicLeg.label>bionic leg</BionicLeg.label>
<BionicLeg.description>Bionic leg uses cutting-edge technology to give its owner extreme walking comfort and strength.</BionicLeg.description>

<BionicArm.label>bionic arm</BionicArm.label>
<BionicArm.description>One of the most sophisticated arm replacements. Gives extreme strength to its user.</BionicArm.description>

<BionicSpine.label>bionic spine</BionicSpine.label>
<BionicSpine.description>This light and impressing device can replace a damaged spine.</BionicSpine.description>

<BionicEar.label>bionic ear</BionicEar.label>
<BionicEar.description>An advanced device that expands upon the basic functions of the ear drum.</BionicEar.description>

<PowerClaw.label>power claw</PowerClaw.label>
<PowerClaw.description>Powerful hand replacement consisting of three deadly claws.</PowerClaw.description>

<BionicHand.label>bionic hand</BionicHand.label>
<BionicHand.description>Allows the user to perform tasks even faster than with regular hands.</BionicHand.description>

<BionicFoot.label>bionic foot</BionicFoot.label>
<BionicFoot.description>This prosthesis grants faster walking without stumbling all the time.</BionicFoot.description>

<BionicFinger.label>bionic finger</BionicFinger.label>
<BionicFinger.description>A replacement finger allowing for slightly faster and more precise movement.</BionicFinger.description>

<BionicToe.label>bionic toe</BionicToe.label>
<BionicToe.description>A replacement toe which lets the wearer grip the ground slightly better.</BionicToe.description>

<BionicJaw.label>bionic jaw</BionicJaw.label>
<BionicJaw.description>Aside from a strong set of teeth, this also comes with a voice modulator.</BionicJaw.description>

<SilentJaw.label>silent jaw</SilentJaw.label>
<SilentJaw.description>This version of the bionic jaw comes without a voice modulator, useful for abrasive patients.</SilentJaw.description>

<PowerArm.label>power arm</PowerArm.label>
<PowerArm.description>Unparalleled strength and dexterity, and with retractable claws. This is the ultimate arm upgrade!</PowerArm.description>

</LanguageData>