<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>EPOE-Forked</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>EPIA_EPOE_Forked</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=1949064302</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>


	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>EPOE_Forked_4_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>New set of updates not seen with EPOE-Forked until now. Firstly, HugsLib news feature will now be utilized to keep players up to date, and new mod settings being available with the assistance of the XML Extensions mod.
|img:newsimages/XML_Extensions|caption:XML Extensions mod, made by Imranfish, extends the functionality of XML patch operations, and allows for the easy creation of mod settings.

With XML Extensions active in your mod list, the following EPOE-Forked's add-on modules are now included in the settings, and no longer needs the actual side-mods to customize your game:
- Allow direct crafting
- Direct crafting only
- Remove workbenches
- Legacy mode (written up in a new way to patch)

|New additional settings are:
- Changing between this mod's or vanilla's item textures for artifical body part items
- Disabling the bionic eyes on the colonist's face
- Original EPOE migration mode, to keep the old prosthetic workbench for converting.

The old prosthetic workbench from original EPOE, upon being destroyed (Not deconstructed!) will become a prosthetic workbench and bionic workbench. Simply get a colonist to punch it and get yourself back on track for all your artificial body parts production! Be sure to claim and rearrange your converted workbenches.

|Once you have finished switching over, you should untick the migration mode to remove the redundant building from being loaded anymore when you launch the game.

Rest of patch notes for v4.2.0:
* Correctly assigning the component and advanced component bills to the synthetic nano printer instead of the prosthetic workbench.
* Prosthesis trader now trades synthread, hyperweave, components, advanced components and MA-AI chips.
* Prosthesis trader's inventory of available artificial body parts for sale have been increased in size.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	

</Defs>