<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

<TipSetDef>
	<defName>EPOEForkedTips</defName>
	<tips>
<!-- Workstations -->
<li>Prosthetic workbench can operate without power at 25% production speed. Handy if you don't have enough power or during a solar flare and you need some progress on prosthetic parts!</li>
<li>Bionics workbench can link with a prosthetic workbench, tissue printer and fabrication bench to provide them increased production speed.</li>
<li>Tissue printer can link with a bionics workbench and fabrication bench to provide them increased production speed.</li>

<!-- Items -->
<li>You can cure scars with synthetic tissue and glitterworld medicine. Make sure the allowed medicines are correctly set, or the surgeon may not be able to use the required glitterworld medicine on the patient.</li>
<li>Bad backs and frailty can be cured with neuromuscular framework. You will need the Synthetic Repair research to make them. They require glitterworld medicines, hyperweave and advanced components to manufacture.</li>
<li>Dementia and Alzheimers can be cured with neuro-cure framework. You will need the Neurological Treatment research to make them. They require glitterworld medicines, hyperweave, neuromuscular framework and MA-AI chips to manufacture.</li>
<li>MA-AI chip (Medical Assistant AI chip) are EPOE's form of a tier 3 component, above advanced component. They are required for the most advanced medical items. They can be acquired from converting an AI subpersona core into 5 of them, or a end-game research unlock their crafting recipe.</li>
<li>Broken scyther blades can be acquired from dismantling Scyther mechanoids. They can be smelted for further plasteel, or restore them into Scyther blades that you can use for other prosthetic items. (EPOE-Forked mod and expansions)</li>
<li>Organic Optimizers nanobots are a new category of body upgrades. The Instinct Optimizers have unique benefits on different body parts. Body purists are safe to receive them, whilst Transhumanists abhor them.</li>
<li>You can have as many different implants you want on a natural body part. Go crazy on installing as many different rib or brain implants on a single colonist!</li>
	</tips>
</TipSetDef>

</Defs>