<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

<SimpleRib.label>blank rib replacement</SimpleRib.label>
<SimpleRib.description>A hollow artificial rib, with a tiny dispenser system. Ready to be filled to complete a rib replacement implant of choice.</SimpleRib.description>

<MedicalRib.label>medical rib replacement</MedicalRib.label>
<MedicalRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little blood filters and antibiotics-dispensers to keep the user healthy.</MedicalRib.description>

<DruggedRib.label>drugged rib replacement</DruggedRib.label>
<DruggedRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little flake-dispensers to keep the user happy. Synthetic liver highly recommended.</DruggedRib.description>

<AdrenalineRib.label>adrenaline rib replacement</AdrenalineRib.label>
<AdrenalineRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little adrenaline-dispensers to keep the user fit and awake.</AdrenalineRib.description>

<PainkillerRib.label>painkiller rib replacement</PainkillerRib.label>
<PainkillerRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little morphine-dispensers to numb the user's pain.</PainkillerRib.description>

<HeaterRib.label>heating rib replacement</HeaterRib.label>
<HeaterRib.description>An artificial rib, containing a micro-reactor powered, heat inducing spiral to warm the body from the inside.</HeaterRib.description>

<CoolerRib.label>cooling rib replacement</CoolerRib.label>
<CoolerRib.description>An artificial rib with a micro coolant system, increasing the effectiveness of heat exchange via dermal exhausts.</CoolerRib.description>

<CoagulatorRib.label>coagulator rib replacement</CoagulatorRib.label>
<CoagulatorRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little coagulator-dispensers that responds to blood loss, which will make the blood clot easier, in an effort to reduce bleeding.</CoagulatorRib.description>

<RespirationRib.label>respiration rib replacement</RespirationRib.label>
<RespirationRib.description>An artificial rib, that works with the diaphragm to assist with regulating breathing pattern for increased efficiency and coping with stress.</RespirationRib.description>

<WakeUpRib.label>wake-up rib replacement</WakeUpRib.label>
<WakeUpRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little wake-up-dispensers to keep the user awake and focused.</WakeUpRib.description>

</LanguageData>