<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Expanded Prosthetics and Organ Engineering - Forked</name>
	<author>Victorique, Aurani, Tarojun</author>
    <url>https://github.com/Aurani/EPOE-Forked</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>vat.epoeforked</packageId>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
		<li>Imranfish.XMLExtensions</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>Ykara.EPOE</li>
		<li>Rah.RBSE</li>
		<li>Rah.RBSEHC</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<description>Adds the ability to craft tons of prosthesis and artificial organs in various forms and shapes. Version 4.3.2.

New option settings available if XML Extension mod is active, available on Steam workshop at:
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2574315206
It comes built in options for Remove workbenches, Allow direct crafting, Direct crafting only and Legacy mode, so you no longer require the add-on modules if you have this active and simply use the mods settings to apply them.

Features:
* Three prosthetic workbench: Prosthetic workbench (Rimworld 1.3 or older), Bionic workbench and Synthetic nano printer.
* The workbenches can link up with each other and the Fabrication workbench to improve production speed.
* Patches for Cyber Fauna and Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Production to allow additional link ups.
* Two new orbital ship traders: Prosthesis and Textile trader.
* Ability to additionally harvest Stomach, Eye, Nose, Ear and Jaw body parts. Plays well with QEE.
* Can mince natural body parts for human meat.
* Can heal scars and numerious chronic health conditions. Additional patch to work with Scar Removal Plus mod.
* Some prosthesis can be further upgraded.
* Body purist friendly augmentations in the form of Organic Optimizers and Instinct Optimizers.
* Ability to scrap unwanted prosthesis for materials.

* Different add-on modules to further customize the mod:
  - Royalty DLC expansion, adds new implants and bionics based off the new Royalty DLC content.
  - Alien expansion + patcher, helps expand upon bionic content and certain issues with certain alien race mods.
* The following add-on modules are built-in with using the XML Extension mod, but if you do not use that, then they are:
  - Remove workbenches, adds crafting to vanilla workbenches, but disable building new EPOE workbenches.
  - Allow direct crafting, enables higher tier recipes to be made in one go at the same total costs.
  - Direct crafting only, enables higher tier recipes to be made in one go at the same total costs, and removes upgrading methods.
  - Legacy mode, reverts crafting costs and methods to version 3.3.13 of the mod.

Compared with original EPOE, this mod will see continued development and rebalancing, active bug fixes, and strives to follow vanilla's standard.</description>
</ModMetaData>