<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

<BasicProsthetics.label>Basic prosthetics</BasicProsthetics.label>
<BasicProsthetics.description>Understanding the basic shape of different body parts and combining that knowledge with basic woodworking, you can now use directly install basic prosthesis.

Peg legs, wooden feet, wooden hands, dentures, eye patch and ear bandages are direct surgeries with a single wood log or textile.

Hook hand and steel arm are crafted at a smithy.</BasicProsthetics.description>

<AdvancedBionics.label>advanced bionics</AdvancedBionics.label>
<AdvancedBionics.description>Upgrade regular bionics to make them even better. Unlocks new recipes on the bionics workbench.</AdvancedBionics.description>

<RibReplacements.label>rib replacements</RibReplacements.label>
<RibReplacements.description>Discovering the concept of very small dispensers, you think about putting them in ribs. You can now craft and install rib implants.</RibReplacements.description>

<SurrogateOrgans.label>surrogate organs</SurrogateOrgans.label>
<SurrogateOrgans.description>Gaining higher medical and technical knowledge, creating a 3D printer to craft simple surrogate organs becomes possible.</SurrogateOrgans.description>

<SyntheticOrgans.label>synthetic organs</SyntheticOrgans.label>
<SyntheticOrgans.description>Further research in nano-technology allows you to print incredibly well-engineered artificial organs. Unlocks new recipes on the tissue printer.</SyntheticOrgans.description>

<EPOE_SyntheticRepair.label>Synthetic repair</EPOE_SyntheticRepair.label>
<EPOE_SyntheticRepair.description>Further research into nano technology allows you to print incredibly well-engineered artificial tissues and nerves to aid with healing scars, frailty and bad backs. Unlocks synthetic tissue and neuromuscular framework recipes on the tissue printer.</EPOE_SyntheticRepair.description>

<EPOE_NeurologicalTreatment.label>Neurological treatment</EPOE_NeurologicalTreatment.label>
<EPOE_NeurologicalTreatment.description>Extensive research into nano technology allows you to print incredibly well-engineered framework kit consisting of artificial adaptable brain tissues, nerves and nanomachines to aid with countering dementia and alzheimer. Unlocks neuro-cure framework recipe on the tissue printer.\n\nNeuro-cure framework only cures dementia and alzheimer, and does not prevent it from appearing again.</EPOE_NeurologicalTreatment.description>

<BrainSurgery.label>brain surgery</BrainSurgery.label>
<BrainSurgery.description>Allows you to perform surgery on the brain.</BrainSurgery.description>

<EPOE_Glitterworld_Implants.label>Glitterworld implants</EPOE_Glitterworld_Implants.label>
<EPOE_Glitterworld_Implants.description>Allows you to make Glitterworld implants.</EPOE_Glitterworld_Implants.description>

<EPOE_AIPersonaCoreImplant.label>AI persona core implant</EPOE_AIPersonaCoreImplant.label>
<EPOE_AIPersonaCoreImplant.description>Allows you to perform the surgery to implant an AI persona core into the brain. It provides a powerful consciousness boost with the assistance of the AI, but it will require regular medical maintenance to avoid the AI turning rogue on the user.</EPOE_AIPersonaCoreImplant.description>

<EPOE_OrganicOptimizer.label>Organic optimization</EPOE_OrganicOptimizer.label>
<EPOE_OrganicOptimizer.description>Allows you to develop nanobots to optimize and bring out the full potential of the natural body, specifically designed to aid body purists.</EPOE_OrganicOptimizer.description>

<EPOE_MAAIChip.label>MA-AI chip</EPOE_MAAIChip.label>
<EPOE_MAAIChip.description>Allows you to manufacture your own MA-AI chip (Medical Assistant-AI chip), without needing to find an AI persona core.</EPOE_MAAIChip.description>

</LanguageData>