<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

<GoldenEye.label>golden eye</GoldenEye.label>
<GoldenEye.description>An eye prosthesis made out of gold. An exorbitant way to cover up a missing eye.</GoldenEye.description>

<LightReceptor.label>light receptor</LightReceptor.label>
<LightReceptor.description>An eye prosthesis. The optic nerves recieve stimulation from the light sensors and signal processors, creating a sensation of vision. It's not as good as a natural eye, but it's a lot better than being blind.</LightReceptor.description>

<SimpleSpine.label>replacement spine</SimpleSpine.label>
<SimpleSpine.description>A spine prosthesis. Highly advanced for its time, can be considered as an early bionic prototype with the first sophisticated application of neural interface in a prosthesis. Still, it is inferior to a real spine</SimpleSpine.description>

<SimpleProstheticHand.label>prosthetic hand</SimpleProstheticHand.label>
<SimpleProstheticHand.description>A hand prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real hand.</SimpleProstheticHand.description>

<SimpleProstheticFoot.label>prosthetic foot</SimpleProstheticFoot.label>
<SimpleProstheticFoot.description>A foot prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real foot.</SimpleProstheticFoot.description>

<SimpleProstheticFinger.label>prosthetic finger</SimpleProstheticFinger.label>
<SimpleProstheticFinger.description>Archaic and crude replacement for lost fingers. Not terribly efficient and certainly not comfortable, but gets the job done.</SimpleProstheticFinger.description>

<SimpleProstheticToe.label>prosthetic toe</SimpleProstheticToe.label>
<SimpleProstheticToe.description>Archaic and crude replacement for lost toes. Inefficient and uncomfortable, they generate a lot of noise while walking, but they get the job done.</SimpleProstheticToe.description>

<HydraulicJaw.label>hydraulic jaw</HydraulicJaw.label>
<HydraulicJaw.description>A jaw prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Food is crushed and chewed more efficiently, but the finer details of speaking is slightly lacking.</HydraulicJaw.description>

<ArtificialNose.label>artificial nose</ArtificialNose.label>
<ArtificialNose.description>A nose prosthesis. Used to cover where the missing nose was on the face.</ArtificialNose.description>

<ReplacementRadius.label>replacement radius</ReplacementRadius.label>
<ReplacementRadius.description>A replacement for the radius, a bone in the lower arm.</ReplacementRadius.description>

<EPIA_ScytherBlade.label>scyther blade</EPIA_ScytherBlade.label>
<EPIA_ScytherBlade.description>Weaponized hand implant utilizing a telescoping blade. Scavenged and restored from a dead scyther mechanoid. Not very comfortable, but quite effective as a close-range weapon.</EPIA_ScytherBlade.description>

</LanguageData>