<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

<AdvancedBionicEye.label>advanced bionic eye</AdvancedBionicEye.label>
<AdvancedBionicEye.description>An ultra advanced artifical eye, further improved from the standard models. With its biogel nerve-link, internal signal pre-processor, and wide-spectrum sensors, it is better than a biological eye in almost every way. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage.</AdvancedBionicEye.description>

<AdvancedBionicArm.label>advanced bionic arm</AdvancedBionicArm.label>
<AdvancedBionicArm.description>An ultra advanced artificial arm, further improved from the standard models. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological arm in almost every way.</AdvancedBionicArm.description>

<AdvancedBionicLeg.label>advanced bionic leg</AdvancedBionicLeg.label>
<AdvancedBionicLeg.description>An ultra advanced artificial leg, further improved from the standard models. With its biogel nerve-link, powerful mini-servos, and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological leg in almost every way.</AdvancedBionicLeg.description>

<AdvancedBionicSpine.label>advanced bionic spine</AdvancedBionicSpine.label>
<AdvancedBionicSpine.description>An ultra advanced artificial spine, further improved from the standard models. A biogel nerve bundle runs down an articulated plasteel core, surrounded by a lattice-dust healing system. It is better than a biological spine in almost every way.</AdvancedBionicSpine.description>

<AdvancedBionicEar.label>advanced bionic ear</AdvancedBionicEar.label>
<AdvancedBionicEar.description>An ultra advanced artificial ear implant, further improved from the standard models. A collection of invisible subdermal microphones capture sound and transmit it to a biogel nerve interface that links directly with the auditory nerve. It's sensitive enough to hear a cat before you see it, can't be damaged by loud noise, and automatically tunes itself to pick out meaningful sounds in noisy environments.</AdvancedBionicEar.description>

<AdvancedBionicHand.label>advanced bionic hand</AdvancedBionicHand.label>
<AdvancedBionicHand.description>An ultra advanced artificial hand, further improved from the standard models. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological hand in almost every way.</AdvancedBionicHand.description>

<AdvancedBionicFoot.label>advanced bionic foot</AdvancedBionicFoot.label>
<AdvancedBionicFoot.description>An ultra advanced artificial foot, further improved from the standard models. With its biogel nerve-link, powerful mini-servos, and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological foot in almost every way.</AdvancedBionicFoot.description>

<AdvancedBionicFinger.label>advanced bionic finger</AdvancedBionicFinger.label>
<AdvancedBionicFinger.description>An ultra advanced artificial finger, further improved from the standard models. Delicate sensors and high-speed wireless transmitters running through the thick, yet lightweight plasteel casing ensure the best precision and grip, far surpassing that of a biological finger.</AdvancedBionicFinger.description>

<AdvancedBionicToe.label>advanced bionic toe</AdvancedBionicToe.label>
<AdvancedBionicToe.description>An ultra advanced artificial toe, further improved from the standard models. Delicate sensors and high-speed wireless transmitters running through the thick, yet lightweight plasteel casing make these toes unrivalled when it comes to movement and control, far surpassing that of biological toes.</AdvancedBionicToe.description>

<AdvancedBionicJaw.label>advanced bionic jaw</AdvancedBionicJaw.label>
<AdvancedBionicJaw.description>An ultra advanced artificial jaw, further improved from the standard models. Silenced mini-servos give great jaw strength, while a voice modulator gives exquisite fine tuning to speech. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological jaw in almost every way.</AdvancedBionicJaw.description>

<AdvancedPowerArm.label>advanced power arm</AdvancedPowerArm.label>
<AdvancedPowerArm.description>A ultra advanced combat-oriented arm replacement consisting of a mechanical hand with a hooked claw on each finger. It cuts deep, and it is strong enough to crush a skull like a hand crushes an egg. The claws can be retracted, making it as useful as a natural hand for non-combat tasks.</AdvancedPowerArm.description>

<ExoskeletonSuit.label>exoskeleton suit</ExoskeletonSuit.label>
<ExoskeletonSuit.description>A high tech device made out of two components: a light skeletal structure to relieve the back and servomotors to make the user stronger.</ExoskeletonSuit.description>

<EPIA_ProtectiveExoskeleton.label>protective exoskeleton</EPIA_ProtectiveExoskeleton.label>
<EPIA_ProtectiveExoskeleton.description>A high tech device made out of a light skeletal structure and servomotors to support itself and the damage mitigation system used to protect the user.</EPIA_ProtectiveExoskeleton.description>

</LanguageData>